A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20 FA292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Files, 1920-1993; 2; 242 Box(es)
  - Turner, Arthur - 1948 - Scotland - American History, 1948-1975 (Box 217, Folder 1744)
  - Turner, Charles - 1934 - Wales - Engineering, 1933-1975 (Box 217, Folder 1745)
  - Turner, James - 1961 - England - Chemistry, 1960-1984 (Box 217, Folder 1746)
  - Turner, John - 1972 - England - International Relations, 1972-1979 (Box 217, Folder 1747)
  - Tyler, Brian Henry Charles - 1966 - New Zealand - Public Administration, 1965-1984 (Box 217, Folder 1748)
  - Tyndale-Briscoe, Ronald - 1933 - England - Geology, 1933-1985 (Box 217, Folder 1749)
  - Uhr, John - 1985 - Australia - Public Administration, 1984-1987 (Box 218, Folder 1750)
  - Ullman, Marc - 1959 - France - Economics, 1959-1977 (Box 218, Folder 1751)
  - Underwood, Eric - 1936 - England - Biochemistry, 1936-1981 (Box 218, Folder 1752)
  - Unschuld, Paul - 1973 - Germany - Medicine/Health Care, 1972-1987 (Box 218, Folder 1753)
  - Unsworth, Susan - 1981 - England - International Relations, 1980-1989 (Box 218, Folder 1754)
  - Upson, Roger - 1960 - England - Business Administration, 1959-1987 (Box 218, Folder 1755)
  - Vale, Vivian - 1952 - England - History, 1951-1984 (Box 218, Folder 1756)
  - Van Andel, Hendikus Harold - 1969 - Netherlands - Business Administration, 1969-1986 (Box 218, Folder 1757)
  - Van Avermaet, Eddy Frans Aline - 1971 - Belgium - Social Psychology, 1971-1980 (Box 218, Folder 1758)
  - Van Bentham van den Bergh, Godfried - 1964 - Netherlands - Political Science, 1962-1975 (Box 219, Folder 1759)
  - Van Bremen, Jan Gerhard - 1971 - Netherlands - Cultural Anthropology, 1971-1987 (Box 219, Folder 1760)
  - Van Broekhoven, Emiel Josef Jan - 1967 - Belgium - Economics, 1966-1967 (Box 219, Folder 1761)
  - Van den Elshout, Anny - 1954 - Netherlands - Law, 1954-1980 (Box 219, Folder 1762)
  - Van den Eynde, Jean - 1976 - Belgium - Law, 1976-1987 (Box 219, Folder 1763)
  - Van der Auwera, Johan - 1975 - Belgium - Linguistics, 1975-1986 (Box 219, Folder 1764)
  - Van Heyningen, William - 1936 - England - Biochemistry, 1936-1987 (Box 219, Folder 1765)
  - Vanistandael, Frans - 1967 - Belgium - Law, 1966-1980 (Box 219, Folder 1766)
  - Van Leeuwen, Wilhelmus - 1954 - Netherlands - Literature, 1952-1975 (Box 220, Folder 1767)
  - Van Obberghen, Emmanuel - 1974 - Belgium - Medicine, 1974-1978 (Box 220, Folder 1768)
  - Van Tol, Gerardus - 1970 - Netherlands - Theatre, 1970-1983 (Box 220, Folder 1769)
  - Van Traa, Maarten - 1970 - Netherlands - Journalism, 1970-1973 (Box 220, Folder 1770)
  - Van Vliet, Nicolaas Jan - 1961 - Netherlands - Mass Communications, 1960-1980 (Box 220, Folder 1771)
  - Van Vulpen, Carl - 1959 - Germany - Business and Industrial Relations, 1959-1984 (Box 220, Folder 1772)
  - Van Zyl, Ian Peter - 1989 - England - Dentistry, 1988-1991 (Box 220, Folder 1773)
  - Vaudagna, Maurizio - 1975 - Italy - American History, 1974-1986 (Box 220, Folder 1774)
  - Veale, John - 1949 - England - Music, 1949-1990 (Box 221, Folder 1775)
  - Veevers, John James - 1961 - Australia - Marine Geology, 1961-1985 (Box 221, Folder 1776)
  - Verbeke, John - 1977 - Belgium - Law, 1977-1986 (Box 221, Folder 1777)
  - Veret, Jean-Louis - 1959 - France - Architecture, 1959-1981 (Box 221, Folder 1778)
  - Verheij, Abraham - 1964 - Netherlands - Business Administration, 1964-1980 (Box 221, Folder 1779)
  - Verney, Douglas Vernon - 1953 - England - Political Sociology, 1953-1975 (Box 221, Folder 1780)
  - Verschueren, Jozef - 1975 - Belgium - Linguistics, 1975-1984 (Box 221, Folder 1781)
  - Vigne, Chidlow - 1930 - England - Forestry, 1930-1984 (Box 221, Folder 1782)
  - Vincentini, Claudio - 1973 - Italy - Political Theatre, 1972-1987 (Box 222, Folder 1783)
  - Vinci, Salvatore - 1968 - Italy - Economics, 1968-1975 (Box 222, Folder 1784)
  - Vineall, Nicholas Edward - 1985 - England - History of Science, 1984-1988 (Box 222, Folder 1785)
  - Viner, Nicholas Philip - 1984 - England - Business Administration, 1984-1987 (Box 222, Folder 1786)
  - Vinter, Richard - 1972 - England - Engineering, 1971-1989 (Box 222, Folder 1787)
  - Vogell, Wolrad - 1977 - Germany - Mathematics, 1976-1981 (Box 222, Folder 1788)
  - Volwahsen, Andreas Wolfgang - 1970 - Germany - Architecture, 1969-1986 (Box 222, Folder 1789)
  - Volwahsen, Andreas Wolfgang - 1970 - Germany - Architecture, 1969-1986 (Box 222, Folder 1790)
  - Von Bulow, Hans Reimar - 1955 - Denmark - Labor Relations, 1954-1975 (Box 222, Folder 1791)
  - Von Der Gablentz, Otto - 1956 - Germany - Political Sociology, 1954-1980 (Box 223, Folder 1792)
  - Von Oetinger, Bolko - 1972 - Germany - Business Administration, 1972-1979 (Box 223, Folder 1793)
  - Von Oetinger, Bolko - 1972 - Germany - Business Administration, 1972-1979 (Box 223, Folder 1794)
  - Von Randow, Thomas - 1955 - Germany - Mathematics and Statistics, 1955-1981 (Box 223, Folder 1795)
  - Von Wangenheim, Eberhard - 1967 - Germany - Economics, 1966-1986 (Box 223, Folder 1796)
  - Waardenburg, Johannes George - 1963 - Netherlands - Development Planning, 1959-1981 (Box 223, Folder 1797)
  - Waddell, Alan - 1956 - Scotland - Business Administration, 1955-1985 (Box 223, Folder 1798)
  - Wade, George - 1957 - Australia - Plant Pathology, 1957-1985 (Box 223, Folder 1799)
  - Wager, Vincent - 1938 - England - Plant Pathology, 1938-1980 (Box 224, Folder 1800)
  - Wagland, Keith - 1959 - England - Architecture, 1958-1986 (Box 224, Folder 1801)
  - Wagner, Rudolph - 1969 - Germany - Chinese Studies, 1967-1987 (Box 224, Folder 1802)
  - Wahl, John - 1949 - South Africa - English Literature, 1949-1970 (Box 224, Folder 1803)
  - Walke, Harold - 1935 - England - Nuclear Physics, 1935-1949 (Box 224, Folder 1804)
  - Walker, Darcy - 1949 - New Zealand - Physics, 1949-1982 (Box 224, Folder 1805)
  - Walker, David Frederick - 1977 - England - Public Administration, 1976-1990 (Box 224, Folder 1806)
  - Walker, John Graham - 1969 - England - Painting, 1968-1990 (Box 224, Folder 1807)
  - Walker, Martin - 1969 - England - History and Politics, 1968-1989 (Box 225, Folder 1808)
  - Walker, Timothy - 1971 - England - Chemistry, 1970-1990 (Box 225, Folder 1809)
  - Wall, Charles - 1960 - England - Mathematics, 1959-1983 (Box 225, Folder 1810)
  - Wallace, Andrew - 1950 - England - Mathematics, 1950-1987 (Box 225, Folder 1811)
  - Wallace, David James - 1970 - England - Mathematical Physics, 1969-1986 (Box 225, Folder 1812)
  - Wallace, Patrick - 1982 - England - Law, 1981-1987 (Box 225, Folder 1813)
  - Wallace-Crabbe, Christopher - 1965 - Australia - Literature, 1964-1982 (Box 226, Folder 1814)
  - Walter, Hartmut - 1967 - Germany - Ecology, 1966-1975 (Box 226, Folder 1815)
  - Wanganeen, Kenneth Hurtle - 1978 - Australia - Anthropology and Sociology, 1978-1981 (Box 226, Folder 1816)
  - Warburton, Daniel - 1985 - England - Music, 1984-1988 (Box 226, Folder 1817)
  - Ward, Dennis - 1927 - England - History, 1928-1955 (Box 226, Folder 1818)
  - Waring, Hugh Douglas - 1952 - England - Forestry, 1951-1975 (Box 226, Folder 1819)
  - Warneke, Robert - 1966 - Australia - Biology, 1965-1975 (Box 226, Folder 1820)
  - Warner, Norman Reginald - 1971 - England - Health Administration, 1970-1987 (Box 226, Folder 1821)
  - Warren, Charles Hugh - 1957 - England - Hypersonic Aerodynamics, 1957-1988 (Box 227, Folder 1822)
  - Warren, Harry - 1929 - England - Geology, 1929-1988 (Box 227, Folder 1823)
  - Warrington, Ian - 1974 - New Zealand - Horticulture, 1973-1985 (Box 227, Folder 1824)
  - Wass, Douglas - 1958 - England - Economics, 1958-1990 (Box 227, Folder 1825)
  - Waterhouse, Ellis - 1927 - England - History of Art, 1927-1985 (Box 227, Folder 1826)
  - Wathelet, Melchoir - 1975 - Belgium - Law, 1975-1984 (Box 227, Folder 1827)
  - Watkins, John - 1979 - England - Medicine, 1978-1988 (Box 227, Folder 1828)
  - Watson, Eric - 1939 - England - Botany, 1939-1975 (Box 227, Folder 1829)
  - Watt, Ian - 1946 - England - English, 1946-1980 (Box 228, Folder 1830)
  - Watt, John - 1950 - New Zealand - Agriculture, 1949-1979 (Box 228, Folder 1831)
  - Watts, Philip - 1953 - England - Economics, 1953-1985 (Box 228, Folder 1832)
  - Watts, Philip - 1953 - England - Economics, 1953-1985 (Box 228, Folder 1833)
  - Watters, Andrew - 1929 - England - Chemistry, 1929-1985 (Box 228, Folder 1834)
  - Weaire, Denis - 1964 - Scotland - Physics, 1963-1975 (Box 228, Folder 1835)
  - Webb, Richard - 1940 - England - History, 1940-1975 (Box 229, Folder 1836)
  - Weber, Rudolph - 1958 - Germany - Architecture, 1957-1980 (Box 229, Folder 1837)
  - Webster, Steven - 1976 - England - Law, 1976-1980 (Box 229, Folder 1838)
  - Weddell, Alexander Graham - 1934 - England - Medicine, 1934-1976 (Box 229, Folder 1839)
  - Weedon, William - 1965 - Australia - Architecture, 1964-1980 (Box 229, Folder 1840)
  - Weir, Alan John - 1952 - England - Mathematics, 1951-1985 (Box 229, Folder 1841)
  - Weir, Alastair James - 1954 - England - Psychology, 1954-1966 (Box 229, Folder 1842)
  - Weir, John Anthony - 1960 - England - Law, 1959-1979 (Box 229, Folder 1843)
  - Weiss, Lionel Edward - 1951 - England - Geology, 1950-1970 (Box 230, Folder 1844)
  - Weitmayer, Horst - 1957 - Germany - Architecture, 1956-1982 (Box 230, Folder 1845)
  - Welch, Garth de Burgh - 1965 - Australia - Choreographic Art, 1965-1985 (Box 230, Folder 1846)
  - Weldon, Peter - 1967 - England - Ceramics, 1967-1986 (Box 230, Folder 1847)
  - Wellenreuther, Hermann - 1968 - Germany - American History, 1964-1984 (Box 230, Folder 1848)
  - Wellenreuther, Hermann - 1968 - Germany - American History, 1964-1984 (Box 230, Folder 1849)
  - Wellenreuther, Hermann - 1968 - Germany - American History, 1964-1984 (Box 230, Folder 1850)
  - Wells, Patricia - 1962 - England - Sociology, 1962-1990 (Box 231, Folder 1851)
  - Wessels, Cornelious Cloete - 1935 - South Africa - Veterinary Medicine, 1935-1986 (Box 231, Folder 1852)
  - Westphal, Eric - 1963 - France - Public Administration, 1961-1975 (Box 231, Folder 1853)
  - Wetherall, Alan - 1957 - England - Physics, 1956-1982 (Box 231, Folder 1854)
  - Wetherfield, Alison - 1984 - England - Law, 1983-1990 (Box 231, Folder 1855)
  - Weymuller, Stanislas Bruno - 1971 - France - Operations Research, 1970-1981 (Box 231, Folder 1856)
  - Wharton, James - 1963 - Australia - Fisheries and Wildlife Management, 1962-1986 (Box 231, Folder 1857)
  - Wheatley, Peter - 1949 - England - Chemistry, 1949-1988 (Box 231, Folder 1858)
  - Whiffen, David - 1946 - England - Chemistry, 1946-1986 (Box 231, Folder 1859)
  - Whimp, John - 1967 - Australia - Theology, 1966-1975 (Box 232, Folder 1860)
  - Whinerary, Wilson - 1967 - New Zealand - Business Studies, 1966-1975 (Box 232, Folder 1861)
  - Whitbread, Robert - 1963 - England - Plant Pathology, 1962-1986 (Box 232, Folder 1862)
  - White, Anthony Alfred - 1980 - England - Energy Studies, 1979-1988 (Box 232, Folder 1863)
  - White, Adam - 1977 - England - Journalism, 1976-1984 (Box 232, Folder 1864)
  - White, Beatrice - 1929 - England - Literature, 1929-1986 (Box 232, Folder 1865)
  - White, Dick - 1928 - England - American History, 1928-1980 (Box 232, Folder 1866)
  - White, John Peter - 1969 - Australia - Anthropology, 1969-1985 (Box 232, Folder 1867)
  - White, Kenneth - 1935 - England - Economics, 1936-1940 (Box 233, Folder 1868)
  - White, Roger - 1969 - England - Architecture, 1968-1988 (Box 233, Folder 1869)
  - Whitehead, John Henry - 1929 - England - Mathematics, 1929-1962 (Box 233, Folder 1870)
  - Whitehouse, Martin John - 1987 - England - Geology, 1986-1989 (Box 233, Folder 1871)
  - Whiteley, Brett - 1967 - Australia - Painting, 1966-1985 (Box 233, Folder 1872)
  - Whitson, Agnes - 1928 - England - History, 1928-1988 (Box 233, Folder 1873)
  - Whittington, Harry - 1938 - England - Geology, 1938-1983 (Box 233, Folder 1874)
  - Wienands, Rudolf - 1966 - Germany - Architecture, 1966-1975 (Box 233, Folder 1875)
  - Wiggins, Anthony John - 1969 - England - Economic Policy, 1966-1990 (Box 233, Folder 1876)
  - Wigham, Trevor - 1974 - England - Comparative Endocrinology, 1973-1977 (Box 234, Folder 1877)
  - Wild, William - 1930 - England - Physical Chemistry, 1930-1979 (Box 234, Folder 1878)
  - Wilde, Georgina - 1978 - England - East Asian Studies, 1977-1982 (Box 234, Folder 1879)
  - Wilkinson, Bruce - 1977 - New Zealand - Economics, 1976-1986 (Box 234, Folder 1880)
  - Wilkinson, John - 1935 - England - Biological Sciences, 1935-1988 (Box 234, Folder 1881)
  - Williams, Alwyn - 1947 - England - Geology, 1947-1989 (Box 234, Folder 1882)
  - Williams, David - 1956 - England - Law, 1955-1989 (Box 234, Folder 1883)
  - Williams, Evan Gwyn - 1931 - England - Astrophysics, 1931-1934 (Box 234, Folder 1884)
  - Williams, Howel - 1926 - England - Geology, 1926-1981 (Box 234, Folder 1885)
  - Williams, Jeffrey - 1973 - England - Biochemistry, 1972-1985 (Box 234, Folder 1886)
  - Williams, John - 1947 - England - Agriculture, 1939-1958 (Box 234, Folder 1887)
  - Williams, Michael - 1967 - England - Electrical Engineering, 1967-1980 (Box 235, Folder 1888)
  - Williams, Raymond Lloyd - 1953 - England - Chemistry, 1952-1987 (Box 235, Folder 1889)
  - Williams, Robert - 1957 - New Zealand - Mathematics, 1957-1982 (Box 235, Folder 1890)
  - Williams, Ronald - 1935 - England - Chemistry, 1932-1985 (Box 235, Folder 1891)
  - Williams, Roy - 1963 - England - Business and Industrial Studies, 1962-1989 (Box 235, Folder 1892)
  - Williams, Roy - 1963 - England - Business and Industrial Studies, 1962-1989 (Box 235, Folder 1893)
  - Williamson, John - 1925 - Scotland - Mathematics, 1925-1950 (Box 235, Folder 1894)
  - Williamson, John Hunter - 1955 - England - Mathematics, 1954-1985 (Box 235, Folder 1895)
  - Williamson, Thomas - 1958 - England - Health Insurance, 1958-1985 (Box 236, Folder 1896)
  - Willis, John - 1930 - England - Law, 1930-1983 (Box 236, Folder 1897)
  - Wills, David - 1931 - England - Economics, 1931-1988 (Box 236, Folder 1898)
  - Willson, Nicholas - 1985 - England - Business Administration, 1984-1988 (Box 236, Folder 1899)
  - Wilson, Basil - 1937 - England - Railway Engineering, 1937-1990 (Box 236, Folder 1900)
  - Wilson, Bryan - 1957 - England - Sociology, 1956-1985 (Box 236, Folder 1901)
  - Wilson, David - 1955 - England - Fluid Mechanics, 1954-1987 (Box 236, Folder 1902)
  - Wilson, Deirdre Susan - 1968 - England - Linguistics, 1967-1979 (Box 236, Folder 1903)
  - Wilson, Edward Guy - 1961 - England - Physics, 1960-1982 (Box 237, Folder 1904)
  - Wilson, Geoffrey - 1960 - England - Law, 1959-1981 (Box 237, Folder 1905)
  - Wilson, Nicholas - 1961 - England - Law, 1960-1982 (Box 237, Folder 1906)
  - Wilson, Roland - 1928 - Australia - Economics, 1927-1975 (Box 237, Folder 1907)
  - Winser, David Michael - 1937 - England - Psychology, 1937-1945 (Box 237, Folder 1908)
  - Winston, Denis - 1932 - England - City Planning, 1932-1980 (Box 237, Folder 1909)
  - Winteringham, Francis - 1951 - England - Biochemistry, 1951-1988 (Box 237, Folder 1910)
  - Wise, Michael David - 1970 - England - Dentistry, 1969-1990 (Box 237, Folder 1911)
  - Wise, Michael David - 1970 - England - Dentistry, 1969-1990 (Box 237, Folder 1912)
  - Wolff, Jonathan - 1985 - England - Philosophy, 1984-1987 (Box 238, Folder 1913)
  - Wood, Adrian - 1967 - England - Economics, 1966-1988 (Box 238, Folder 1914)
  - Wood, Christopher Harald - 1954 - England - Occupational Health, 1953-1985 (Box 238, Folder 1915)
  - Wood, Peter Denis - 1955 - England - Geography, 1954-1980 (Box 238, Folder 1916)
  - Wood, Ronald - 1950 - England - Plant Pathology, 1950-1986 (Box 238, Folder 1917)
  - Woodhead, Arthur Geoffrey - 1947 - England - Greek Epigraphy, 1947-1985 (Box 238, Folder 1918)
  - Woodrow, Ian Edward - 1985 - Australia - Biochemistry, 1984-1986 (Box 238, Folder 1919)
  - Woods, Anthony - 1968 - Australia - Painting, 1968-1982 (Box 238, Folder 1920)
  - Woodward, Donald - 1939 - New Zealand - Public Administration, 1939-1982 (Box 238, Folder 1921)
  - Woodward, Sydney Nicholas - 1965 - England - Business Administration, 1964-1984 (Box 239, Folder 1922)
  - Wooldridge, Adrian - 1984 - England - Educational Psychology, 1983-1986 (Box 239, Folder 1923)
  - Wooldridge, David Humphrey - 1955 - England - Music, 1953-1989 (Box 239, Folder 1924)
  - Wooldridge, David Humphrey - 1955 - England - Music, 1953-1989 (Box 239, Folder 1925)
  - Wooley, Richard - 1929 - England - Astronomy, 1929-1986 (Box 239, Folder 1926)
  - Woomer, Stanley - 1951 - England - Architecture, 1951-1976 (Box 239, Folder 1927)
  - Worms, Jean-Pierre - 1964 - France - Sociology, 1963-1981 (Box 239, Folder 1928)
  - Worthington, John - 1965 - England - Architecture, 1964-1989 (Box 239, Folder 1929)
  - Wright, Alexander William - 1989 - England - Architecture, 1938-1989 (Box 239, Folder 1930)
  - Wright, Esmond - 1938 - England - American History, 1938-1989 (Box 239, Folder 1931)
  - Wright, Lester - 1976 - England - Criminology, 1975-1988 (Box 240, Folder 1932)
  - Wright, Norman - 1926 - England - Dairy Chemistry, 1925-1970 (Box 240, Folder 1933)
  - Wright, Peter - 1937 - England - History, 1937-1976 (Box 240, Folder 1934)
  - Wrinch, Charlotte Mary - 1970 - England - Byzantine Studies, 1968-1990 (Box 240, Folder 1935)
  - Wylie, Shaun - 1934 - England - Mathematics, 1934-1988 (Box 240, Folder 1936)
  - Wyllie, John Hamilton - 1965 - England - Medicine, 1964-1986 (Box 240, Folder 1937)
  - Wynn-Williams, Charles Gareth - 1971 - England - Astronomy, 1970-1979 (Box 240, Folder 1938)
  - Yardley, Bruce - 1974 - England - Geology, 1973-1984 (Box 241, Folder 1939)
  - Youle, Philip - 1938 - England - Chemistry, 1938-1990 (Box 241, Folder 1940)
  - Young, George - 1934 - England - Political Science, 1934-1968 (Box 241, Folder 1941)
  - Young, Hugo - 1963 - England - American Politics, 1962-1989 (Box 241, Folder 1942)
  - Young, Leslie - 1935 - England - Biochemistry, 1935-1988 (Box 241, Folder 1943)
  - Younger, Paul - 1984 - England - Geology, 1983-1990 (Box 241, Folder 1944)
  - Youngson, Alexander - 1947 - Scotland - Economics, 1947-1987 (Box 241, Folder 1945)
  - Yudkin, Michael - 1962 - England - Molecular Biology, 1962-1979 (Box 241, Folder 1946)
  - Zahn, Ernst Frans Joseph - 1958 - Netherlands - Sociology, 1957-1987 (Box 242, Folder 1947)
  - Zander, Benjamin - 1964 - England - Music, 1964-1986 (Box 242, Folder 1948)
  - Zeeman, Erik Christopher - 1954 - England - Mathematics, 1954-1988 (Box 242, Folder 1949)
  - Zucconi, Mario - 1968 - Italy - Philosophy, 1964-1982 (Box 242, Folder 1950)
  - Zupponi, Mario - 1958 - Switzerland - Economics, 1956-1963 (Box 242, Folder 1951)
  - Zwimfer, Laurence - 1979 - New Zealand - Telecommunications, 1978-1981 (Box 242, Folder 1952)